{
    "subject": "resource/Tote_(footballer)",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Madrid",
    "human_readable": "Tote was born in Madrid.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.967920184135437,
            "question": "Is Madrid the place where Tote was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7543795704841614,
            "question": "Where was Tote born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.550381064414978,
            "question": "Which city is known as the birthplace of Tote?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45957431197166443,
            "question": "What city is associated with Tote's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45828479528427124,
            "question": "What is Tote's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33846980333328247,
            "question": "Can you tell me Tote's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33251601457595825,
            "question": "To what city does Tote's birth relate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25159063935279846,
            "question": "Where did Tote begin their life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24866676330566406,
            "question": "In which location did Tote come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.191740944981575,
            "question": "What is the city of Tote's origin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tote was born in Madrid.",
            "html": "dbpedia_458_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which location did Tote come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_458_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Tote begin their life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_458_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what city does Tote's birth relate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_458_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_458_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_458/re-ranker-msmarco/83.txt) states:\n\n\"Tote Garc\u00eda Ortega was born in 1915 in Madrid, Madrid, Spain.\"\n\nThis clearly supports the triple \"Tote was born in Madrid.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information states, \"Tote Garc\u00eda Ortega was born in 1915 in Madrid, Madrid, Spain,\" which supports the triple that Tote was born in Madrid."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}